icv2.com 2005-12-10

# ICv2 - Privacy Statement

| 

**_ICv2 Privacy Statement_**

We understand that your privacy is important to you.  That's why we're disclosing our policies here so you can make informed decisions about using the ICv2 site.  We collect information to better understand our users, to help us tailor our site to their needs, to assist our advertisers in communicating with our users, and to make it possible for users to receive our e-mail newsletter, promotional offers, and premiums.  This privacy statement is applicable to GCO, LLC's ("GCO") web site located at [www.ICv2.com](http://www.icv2.com/). 

_Information Collection_

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide this information on a voluntary basis.  We will make every effort to ensure that whatever information you provide will be maintained in a secure environment. 

_Information Sharing_

When we ask for this data, you will have the opportunity to indicate whether you would like to "opt out" of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services, and offerings from us and/or any third parties.  You can also opt out at anytime thereafter. 

However, even if you opt out of receiving any communications from us, we reserve the right to contact you regarding any matter that might affect our service to you, if any, and/or our records on you. 

_Information Use_

We reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics. We do this in order to measure interest in and use of our Web site.  We may share this information with advertisers.  We may also use this information to let advertisers know how many visitors have seen their banners and how many have clicked on them.  We will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties; advertisers will not be able to identify any individual from these analyses. 

We collect IP addresses for system administration, record keeping, and advertising reporting. Your IP address is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the World Wide Web.  Our servers record incoming IP addresses.  The IP addresses are analyzed only in aggregate; no connection is made between you and your computer's IP address.  By tracking IP addresses, we can determine which sites refer the most people to our Web site. (Think of an IP address like your zip code; it tells us in general terms where you're from.) 

_Cookies_

Our site does use "cookies," digital identifiers that we transfer to your hard drive via your browser, which help us identify your computer.  Cookies help us tailor our site to your interests.  Once we open "industry only" areas of our site (for example industry-only discussion boards), cookies will also allow you access without logging in each time.  If you wish, you may disable the cookies using your browser software.  Check the help area of your browser (usually accessible through a button on the toolbar) for information on disabling cookies.

_We ask for permission_

We will not e-mail you without your permission.  During the registration process, you will be asked whether or not you wish to receive ICv2's Headline News -- our weekly compendium of the top headlines affecting the industry -- and occasional promotional offers.  If you elect to begin receiving our materials and wish to stop at any time, just follow the unsubscribe instructions in each e-mail we send.  __

_Our Security Policy_

We are aware of your privacy concerns and strive to collect only as much data as is required to make your Internet and/or product use experience as efficient and satisfying as possible, in the most unobtrusive manner as possible. 

The foregoing policies are effective as of January 1, 2001. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement.  This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
